Starohorodskyi Dmitriy

Unity Developer

Work history

Unity Developer

Ejaw

09.2020 - PRESENT

My responsibilities include:

- Building an application to Android
- Optimizing graphics performance
- Introduction of new game mechanics
- Ensuring that the game design is fully implemented and performs as expected.

Unity Developer

Kodisoft

07.2016 - 08.2020

My responsibilities included:

- Game application development
- Setup the Unity engine to work in the UWP
- Writing libraries for working with local frameworks

Education

Bachelor Diploma

Kyiv Polytechnic Institute

09.2016 - 07.2020

Chemical Engineering Faculty. Department of technical and software of automation.

Contact details

Prague 38 068 740 23 22 catereiptsi@gmail.com

Personal Profile

I have 2 years of experience in desktop application development and half a year of experience in mobile application development

I have experience in developing an application architecture from scratch and supporting and implementing new elements into an existing application

Skills

Unity



C#



Git

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$

Adobe Photoshop

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$

Languages

English - Pre-intermediate

Russian - Native

Ukrainian - Native

Czech - Pre-intermediate